MINJEE KIM

937 Progress Avenue, Scarborough, ON M1G 3T8 (236) 993-5906 • mkim276@my.centennialcollege.ca

PROFILE:

A collaborative and detail-oriented student of Software Engineering Technology, specializing in Artificial Intelligence, who is passionate for learning new technologies. Possesses skills in object-oriented programming, interface design and knowledge of the software development life cycle.

SKILLS OVERVIEW:

Programming Languages: HTML5/CSS, JavaScript, Python, SQL, C#, Java

Operating Systems: Windows, Unix, Linux

Software/Tools: MS Office, Git/GitHub, Angular, MongoDB, Node.js

- Gaining foundations of AI concepts: algorithms, cloud computing, machine learning, and deep learning
- Effectively works both within team environments and independently with excellent time management
- Multilingual with fluency in English and Korean

EDUCATION

Advanced Diploma in Software Engineering Technology - Artificial Intelligence

Jan 2022 - Present

Centennial College, Toronto, ON

Courses: Software Engineering Fundamentals, Web Interface Design, Database Concepts, Client-Slide Web Development, Software Engineering Methodologies, and Unix/Linux OS

ACADEMIC PROJECTS

Web Design – C#, HTML, JavaScript

• Designed a responsive, user-oriented simple image gallery using Ajax and jQuery

Software Requirements Specification

- Collaborated on the planning SRS document for a music app that detects plagiarism
- Collaborated on the planning SRS document for a Second-Hand Product web for centennial students

Second-Hand Product Web Application - ANABADA

• Working on a second-hand products web application that allows users to exchange, buy/sell their second-hand products in the Centennial community to reduce unnecessary waste

WORK EXPERIENCE

Computer Academy - Administrative Assistant

Jan 2021 - April 2021

E-Coding, Gimpo, South Korea

- Gathered information on upcoming computer test events and produced a listing
- Created the academy instruction of coding test guides for students
- Performed general administrative tasks, answering inquiries, data entry, and customer service

Pharmacy Assistant

April 2020 - Oct. 20201

Best Pharmacy, Gimpo, South Korea

- Categorised and organised medicines and medical supplies in accordance with guidelines
- Prepared medication packages according to the prescription form from health providers
- Made lists of the narcotics, medicines, and supplies at the pharmacy for inventory